Hey, what's going on everyone. So I worked
with Ryan Christmas for about two and a
half months as my CSM, and cannot
recommend this guy enough. He was very
well spoken in terms of the English
language, which a lot of us run companies
in. And yeah, he really had diligent
follow-up, got me multiple testimonials,
hopped on multiple Zoom calls, quelled
multiple issues. So really recommend him
for anyone looking for a CSM. And yeah, he
really understood the
construction industry as well. So that
means, you know, any sort of contractor.
I remember specifically one of his calls,
I mentioned some sort of CRM that he knew,
and that instantly creates rapport. And
obviously with CSM, that's very important.
So yeah, highly recommend this guy to
anyone looking for a CSM. And yeah, any
questions, you can always give me a call.